export const irregularVerbsGame = {
  gameId: 1,
  type: 'TranslationGame',
  name: 'Irregular Verbs',
  instructions: 'Translate the verb into all tenses.',
  actions: [
    { placeholder: 'Infinitive', label: 'Infinitive' },
    { placeholder: 'Past', label: 'Past' },
    { placeholder: 'Participle', label: 'Participle' }
  ],
  questions: [
    {
      prompt: 'surgir',
      answers: [{ value: 'arise' }, { value: 'arose' }, { value: 'arisen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'despertarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'awake' }, { value: 'awoke' }, { value: 'awoken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ser',
      answers: [{ value: 'be' }, { value: 'was' }, { value: 'been' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'estar',
      answers: [{ value: 'be' }, { value: 'were' }, { value: 'been' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'soportar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bear' }, { value: 'bore' }, { value: 'born' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'vencer',
      answers: [{ value: 'beat' }, { value: 'beat' }, { value: 'beaten' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'llegar a ser',
      answers: [{ value: 'become' }, { value: 'became' }, { value: 'become' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'empezar',
      answers: [{ value: 'begin' }, { value: 'began' }, { value: 'begun' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'doblar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bend' }, { value: 'bent' }, { value: 'bent' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'apostar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bet' }, { value: 'bet' }, { value: 'bet' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'atar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bind' }, { value: 'bound' }, { value: 'bound' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'pujar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bid' }, { value: 'bid' }, { value: 'bid' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'morder',
      answers: [{ value: 'bite' }, { value: 'bit' }, { value: 'bitten' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sangrar',
      answers: [{ value: 'bleed' }, { value: 'bled' }, { value: 'bled' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'soplar',
      answers: [{ value: 'blow' }, { value: 'blew' }, { value: 'blown' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'romper',
      answers: [{ value: 'break' }, { value: 'broke' }, { value: 'broken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'criar',
      answers: [{ value: 'breed' }, { value: 'bred' }, { value: 'bred' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'traer',
      answers: [{ value: 'bring' }, { value: 'brought' }, { value: 'brought' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'radiar',
      answers: [
        { value: 'broadcast' },
        { value: 'broadcast' },
        { value: 'broadcast' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'construir',
      answers: [{ value: 'build' }, { value: 'built' }, { value: 'built' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'quemar',
      answers: [{ value: 'burn' }, { value: 'burnt' }, { value: 'burnt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'reventar',
      answers: [{ value: 'burst' }, { value: 'burst' }, { value: 'burst' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'comprar',
      answers: [{ value: 'buy' }, { value: 'bought' }, { value: 'bought' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'atrapar',
      answers: [{ value: 'catch' }, { value: 'caught' }, { value: 'caught' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'venir',
      answers: [{ value: 'come' }, { value: 'came' }, { value: 'come' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'costar',
      answers: [{ value: 'cost' }, { value: 'cost' }, { value: 'cost' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'cortar',
      answers: [{ value: 'cut' }, { value: 'cut' }, { value: 'cut' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'elegir',
      answers: [{ value: 'choose' }, { value: 'chose' }, { value: 'chosen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'agarrarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'cling' }, { value: 'clung' }, { value: 'clung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'arrastrarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'creep' }, { value: 'crept' }, { value: 'crept' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'tratar',
      answers: [{ value: 'deal' }, { value: 'dealt' }, { value: 'dealt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'cavar',
      answers: [{ value: 'dig' }, { value: 'dug' }, { value: 'dug' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hacer',
      answers: [{ value: 'do' }, { value: 'did' }, { value: 'done' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dibujar',
      answers: [{ value: 'draw' }, { value: 'drew' }, { value: 'drawn' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'so√±ar',
      answers: [{ value: 'dream' }, { value: 'dreamt' }, { value: 'dreamt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'beber',
      answers: [{ value: 'drink' }, { value: 'drank' }, { value: 'drunk' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'conducir',
      answers: [{ value: 'drive' }, { value: 'drove' }, { value: 'driven' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'comer',
      answers: [{ value: 'eat' }, { value: 'ate' }, { value: 'eaten' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'caer',
      answers: [{ value: 'fall' }, { value: 'fell' }, { value: 'fallen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'alimentar',
      answers: [{ value: 'feed' }, { value: 'fed' }, { value: 'fed' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sentir',
      answers: [{ value: 'feel' }, { value: 'felt' }, { value: 'felt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'luchar',
      answers: [{ value: 'fight' }, { value: 'fought' }, { value: 'fought' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'encontrar',
      answers: [{ value: 'find' }, { value: 'found' }, { value: 'found' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'huir',
      answers: [{ value: 'flee' }, { value: 'fled' }, { value: 'fled' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'volar',
      answers: [{ value: 'fly' }, { value: 'flew' }, { value: 'flown' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'prohibir',
      answers: [
        { value: 'forbid' },
        { value: 'forbade' },
        { value: 'forbidden' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'olvidar',
      answers: [
        { value: 'forget' },
        { value: 'forgot' },
        { value: 'forgotten' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'perdonar',
      answers: [
        { value: 'forgive' },
        { value: 'forgave' },
        { value: 'forgiven' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'congelar',
      answers: [{ value: 'freeze' }, { value: 'froze' }, { value: 'frozen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'obtener',
      answers: [{ value: 'get' }, { value: 'got' }, { value: 'got' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dar',
      answers: [{ value: 'give' }, { value: 'gave' }, { value: 'given' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ir',
      answers: [{ value: 'go' }, { value: 'went' }, { value: 'gone' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'crecer',
      answers: [{ value: 'grow' }, { value: 'grew' }, { value: 'grown' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'moler',
      answers: [{ value: 'grind' }, { value: 'ground' }, { value: 'ground' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'colgar',
      answers: [{ value: 'hang' }, { value: 'hung' }, { value: 'hung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'haber/tener',
      answers: [{ value: 'have' }, { value: 'had' }, { value: 'had' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'oir',
      answers: [{ value: 'hear' }, { value: 'heard' }, { value: 'heard' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ocultar',
      answers: [{ value: 'hide' }, { value: 'hid' }, { value: 'hidden' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'golpear',
      answers: [{ value: 'hit' }, { value: 'hit' }, { value: 'hit' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sostener',
      answers: [{ value: 'hold' }, { value: 'held' }, { value: 'held' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'herir',
      answers: [{ value: 'hurt' }, { value: 'hurt' }, { value: 'hurt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'guardar',
      answers: [{ value: 'keep' }, { value: 'kept' }, { value: 'kept' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'saber',
      answers: [{ value: 'know' }, { value: 'knew' }, { value: 'known' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'arrodillarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'kneel' }, { value: 'knelt' }, { value: 'knelt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'tejer',
      answers: [{ value: 'knit' }, { value: 'knit' }, { value: 'knit' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'tender',
      answers: [{ value: 'lay' }, { value: 'laid' }, { value: 'laid' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'liderar',
      answers: [{ value: 'lead' }, { value: 'led' }, { value: 'led' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'apoyarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'lean' }, { value: 'leant' }, { value: 'leant' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'brincar',
      answers: [{ value: 'leap' }, { value: 'leapt' }, { value: 'leapt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'aprender',
      answers: [{ value: 'learn' }, { value: 'learnt' }, { value: 'learnt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dejar',
      answers: [{ value: 'leave' }, { value: 'left' }, { value: 'left' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'prestar',
      answers: [{ value: 'lend' }, { value: 'lent' }, { value: 'lent' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'permitir',
      answers: [{ value: 'let' }, { value: 'let' }, { value: 'let' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'echarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'lie' }, { value: 'lay' }, { value: 'lain' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'encender',
      answers: [{ value: 'light' }, { value: 'lit' }, { value: 'lit' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'perder',
      answers: [{ value: 'lose' }, { value: 'lost' }, { value: 'lost' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hacer',
      answers: [{ value: 'make' }, { value: 'made' }, { value: 'made' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'significar',
      answers: [{ value: 'mean' }, { value: 'meant' }, { value: 'meant' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'quedar',
      answers: [{ value: 'meet' }, { value: 'met' }, { value: 'met' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'equivocar',
      answers: [
        { value: 'mistake' },
        { value: 'mistook' },
        { value: 'mistaken' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'vencer',
      answers: [
        { value: 'overcome' },
        { value: 'overcame' },
        { value: 'overcome' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'pagar',
      answers: [{ value: 'pay' }, { value: 'paid' }, { value: 'paid' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'poner',
      answers: [{ value: 'put' }, { value: 'put' }, { value: 'put' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'leer',
      answers: [{ value: 'read' }, { value: 'read' }, { value: 'read' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'montar',
      answers: [{ value: 'ride' }, { value: 'rode' }, { value: 'ridden' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'llamar',
      answers: [{ value: 'ring' }, { value: 'rang' }, { value: 'rung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'levantarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'rise' }, { value: 'rose' }, { value: 'risen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'correr',
      answers: [{ value: 'run' }, { value: 'ran' }, { value: 'run' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'decir',
      answers: [{ value: 'say' }, { value: 'said' }, { value: 'said' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ver',
      answers: [{ value: 'see' }, { value: 'saw' }, { value: 'seen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'buscar',
      answers: [{ value: 'seek' }, { value: 'sought' }, { value: 'sought' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'vender',
      answers: [{ value: 'sell' }, { value: 'sold' }, { value: 'sold' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'enviar',
      answers: [{ value: 'send' }, { value: 'sent' }, { value: 'sent' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'poner(se)',
      answers: [{ value: 'set' }, { value: 'set' }, { value: 'set' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'coser',
      answers: [{ value: 'sew' }, { value: 'sewed' }, { value: 'sewed' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sacudir',
      answers: [{ value: 'shake' }, { value: 'shook' }, { value: 'shaken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'esquilar',
      answers: [{ value: 'shear' }, { value: 'shore' }, { value: 'shorn' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'brillar',
      answers: [{ value: 'shine' }, { value: 'shone' }, { value: 'shone' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'disparar',
      answers: [{ value: 'shoot' }, { value: 'shot' }, { value: 'shot' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'mostrar',
      answers: [{ value: 'show' }, { value: 'showed' }, { value: 'shown' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'encogerse',
      answers: [{ value: 'shrink' }, { value: 'shrank' }, { value: 'shrunk' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'cerrar',
      answers: [{ value: 'shut' }, { value: 'shut' }, { value: 'shut' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'cantar',
      answers: [{ value: 'sing' }, { value: 'sang' }, { value: 'sung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hundir',
      answers: [{ value: 'sink' }, { value: 'sank' }, { value: 'sunk' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sentarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'sit' }, { value: 'sat' }, { value: 'sat' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dormir',
      answers: [{ value: 'sleep' }, { value: 'slept' }, { value: 'slept' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'resbalar',
      answers: [{ value: 'slide' }, { value: 'slid' }, { value: 'slid' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'oler',
      answers: [{ value: 'smell' }, { value: 'smelt' }, { value: 'smelt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sembrar',
      answers: [{ value: 'sow' }, { value: 'sowed' }, { value: 'sowed' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hablar',
      answers: [{ value: 'speak' }, { value: 'spoke' }, { value: 'spoken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'acelerar',
      answers: [{ value: 'speed' }, { value: 'sped' }, { value: 'sped' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'deletrear',
      answers: [{ value: 'spell' }, { value: 'spelt' }, { value: 'spelt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'gastar',
      answers: [{ value: 'spend' }, { value: 'spent' }, { value: 'spent' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'derramar',
      answers: [{ value: 'spill' }, { value: 'spilt' }, { value: 'spilt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hilar',
      answers: [{ value: 'spin' }, { value: 'spun' }, { value: 'spun' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'escupir',
      answers: [{ value: 'spit' }, { value: 'spat' }, { value: 'spat' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dividir',
      answers: [{ value: 'split' }, { value: 'split' }, { value: 'split' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'estropear',
      answers: [{ value: 'spoil' }, { value: 'spoilt' }, { value: 'spoilt' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'extender',
      answers: [{ value: 'spread' }, { value: 'spread' }, { value: 'spread' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'saltar',
      answers: [{ value: 'spring' }, { value: 'sprang' }, { value: 'sprung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'estar en pie',
      answers: [{ value: 'stand' }, { value: 'stood' }, { value: 'stood' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'robar',
      answers: [{ value: 'steal' }, { value: 'stole' }, { value: 'stolen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'pegar',
      answers: [{ value: 'stick' }, { value: 'stuck' }, { value: 'stuck' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'picar',
      answers: [{ value: 'sting' }, { value: 'stung' }, { value: 'stung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'apestar',
      answers: [{ value: 'stink' }, { value: 'stank' }, { value: 'stunk' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'dar zancadas',
      answers: [
        { value: 'stride' },
        { value: 'strode' },
        { value: 'stridden' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'golpear',
      answers: [{ value: 'strike' }, { value: 'struck' }, { value: 'struck' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'jurar',
      answers: [{ value: 'swear' }, { value: 'swore' }, { value: 'sworn' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sudar',
      answers: [{ value: 'sweat' }, { value: 'sweat' }, { value: 'sweat' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'barrer',
      answers: [{ value: 'sweep' }, { value: 'swept' }, { value: 'swept' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'hinchar',
      answers: [{ value: 'swell' }, { value: 'swelled' }, { value: 'swollen' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'nadar',
      answers: [{ value: 'swim' }, { value: 'swam' }, { value: 'swum' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'columpiarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'swing' }, { value: 'swung' }, { value: 'swung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'coger',
      answers: [{ value: 'take' }, { value: 'took' }, { value: 'taken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ense√±ar',
      answers: [{ value: 'teach' }, { value: 'taught' }, { value: 'taught' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'rasgar',
      answers: [{ value: 'tear' }, { value: 'tore' }, { value: 'torn' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'decir',
      answers: [{ value: 'tell' }, { value: 'told' }, { value: 'told' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'pensar',
      answers: [{ value: 'think' }, { value: 'thought' }, { value: 'thought' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'arrojar',
      answers: [{ value: 'throw' }, { value: 'threw' }, { value: 'thrown' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'introducir',
      answers: [{ value: 'thrust' }, { value: 'thrust' }, { value: 'thrust' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'pisar',
      answers: [{ value: 'tread' }, { value: 'trod' }, { value: 'trodden' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'entender',
      answers: [
        { value: 'understand' },
        { value: 'understood' },
        { value: 'understood' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'sufrir',
      answers: [
        { value: 'undergo' },
        { value: 'underwent' },
        { value: 'undergone' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'emprender',
      answers: [
        { value: 'undertake' },
        { value: 'undertook' },
        { value: 'undertaken' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'despertarse',
      answers: [{ value: 'wake' }, { value: 'woke' }, { value: 'woken' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'llevar puesto',
      answers: [{ value: 'wear' }, { value: 'wore' }, { value: 'worn' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'tejer',
      answers: [{ value: 'weave' }, { value: 'wove' }, { value: 'woven' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'mojar',
      answers: [{ value: 'wet' }, { value: 'wet' }, { value: 'wet' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'ganar',
      answers: [{ value: 'win' }, { value: 'won' }, { value: 'won' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'enrollar',
      answers: [{ value: 'wind' }, { value: 'wound' }, { value: 'wound' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'retirar',
      answers: [
        { value: 'withdraw' },
        { value: 'withdrew' },
        { value: 'withdrawn' }
      ]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'torcer',
      answers: [{ value: 'wring' }, { value: 'wrung' }, { value: 'wrung' }]
    },
    {
      prompt: 'escribir',
      answers: [{ value: 'write' }, { value: 'wrote' }, { value: 'written' }]
    }
  ]
}
